Hannah Starcevich

(425) 698-8808 | starcevichh@gmail.com | Seattle, WA 98102

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/hannah-starcevich | GitHub: www.github.com/HannahStarcevich |

Portfolio: www.hannah-starcevich.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer specializing in React / JavaScript, with a previous career as a Project Management Consultant at Microsoft. I am known by clients and peers for my sharp attention to detail and motivation to deliver high quality work. Excellent communication skills developed from consulting diverse audiences and teaching English throughout Latin America.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- React.js, Material UI, JSX, Hooks
- MySQL, Sequelize, Mongo DB
- JavaScript, jQuery, Node.Js.
- Axios, AJAX, APIs, JSON
- MERN, Heroku, PWA
- Git, GitHub, CSS3, Html5

Relevant Experience & Projects

Dog Profile and Tracking System React Web Application | Front End Developer | Deployed Site | Github Link

Full stack, responsive web app built with React, Material UI and MySQL Database for the client, a <u>national dog rescue</u>. Site features a login portal for fosters, adopters and staff to create, view and edit the database of dog and user profile details.

- **Role**: Lead project management, client meetings and relationship. Created all wireframes of the site. Developed over 30 React components and 4 site pages with dynamic data visualizations; pie charts, data tables and animations.
- **Utilized**: React, Material UI, Functional Components, JSX, JSON, Axios, Express, MySQL Database, Sequelize, full CRUD functionality, User Authentication / Bcrypt, Node, Nodemailer, GitHub, Git, JavaScript
- Awarded by the UW Boot Camp for the "People's Choice Award" for Best Final Project and Best UI/UX
- Login: testadopter6@asf.com, Password: Password

Employee Directory React Web Application with API | Full Stack Developer | Deployed Site | Github Link

Full stack web app built on React and features the Random User API to search for employees in a worldwide database. The UI is composed of class-based components, responds to user search and sorts data alphabetically.

- Role: Independently designed and developed with React and launched on Heroku, used Axios to search API.
- Utilized: React, JSX, Class-Based Components, Axios, Heroku, Node, Express, Bootstrap, Javascript, JSON, GitHub, Git

Budget Tracker Progressive Web Application | Full Stack Developer | Deployed Site | Github Link

Full stack web app, built using MongoDB and MVC framework that allows users to input transactions, including the name and value to add or subtract from their total budget. Their data is dynamically displayed on the page in a table and graph. Users can input data while offline, inputs are stored in the cache and then uploaded to the site when internet connection is restored.

- Role: Independently designed and developed a budget tracker to include data visualizations that dynamically update.
- **Utilized**: Heroku, MongoDB, Progressive Web App, Service Worker, JSON dependencies, Compression, Express, Lite-Server, Mongoose, Morgan GitHub, Git, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

Pizza Cutter Restaurant Website & Admin Dashboard | Full Stack Developer | Deployed Site | Github Link

Built a new modern site for Pizza Cutter restaurant with menu items stored in MySQL / Sequelize database. Including login portal for the owner to update menu item details and photos through an admin dashboard.

- Role: Led four person team as a project manager and coded both front and back end. Leverage ERD framework for database structuring with full CRUD functionality of menu items that dynamically update the customer facing site
- **Utilized**: Heroku, Sequelize, MySQL, Bcrypt, Express, Express-Session, Cloundinary, Dotenv, Node, Javascript, JSON, Handlebars, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Materialize, GitHub, Git

Professional Experience

Project Management Consultant - Microsoft Corporation, Redmond, WA (*Contracted with <u>AG Consulting Partners</u>*) 8/2018 - 11/2020

Led project management for global Enterprise sales strategy teams at Microsoft.

- Accelerated team success as the business manager of the Senior Director of Enterprise Commercial.
- Led all weekly team meetings for 12 senior business executives and drove momentum across global programs.
- Managed virtual events and program planning for global networks of thousands of Microsoft sellers.
- Led operations and logistics for the Enterprise Commercial quarterly business review cycle for 14 global regions.
- Created communications (PowerPoint and Email) distributed to thousands of Microsoft employees and Partners.
- Synthesized complex data sets to generate advanced PowerBi and Excel reports to inform global strategy.

Led the end to end project management of the development and launch of the AG Consulting Partners Website.

- Identified project scope, created and pitched the website map, content and design to the CEO and partners.
- Interviewed and selected website development team and led partnership through three-month design process.
- Orchestrated the company wide photoshoot and selected all media and images for the site.
- Launched site, maintained content updates such as blog articles and regular updates.

Led pro-bono consulting project, website site design and project management of Ben's Fund Non-Profit Website.

- Led six-month pro-bono consulting project and managed company wide support of the project.
- Designed the site mock up and pitched the site design to the Non-Profit owners and investors.

Volunteer & Work Experience in Latin America

NGO Program Ambassador—Days for Girls International, Panajachel, Guatemala	12/2018
Patagonia National Park Expedition Guide—Tierra Patagonia, Torres del Paine, Chile	12/2017 –
4/2018	
English Language Teacher—Beyond English & Independent Contractor, Santiago, Chile	2/2017 - 12/2017

Education

Full Stack Web Development Certificate

Coding Boot Camp, University of Washington Seattle, WA

10/2020 - 3/2021

9/2012 - 6/2016

Bachelor of Business Administration

University of Washington Foster School of Business, Seattle, WA

- Certificate of International Business: Spanish Track
- Centro de Idiomas: University of Washington, Spanish Study Abroad Program Leon, Spain